Today's video is about PVC clothing and this time for real. It is real PVC. I have catsuits,
I have a raincoat. Really looking forward to it and it's going to be really colorful and fun.
Let's go. Make it kinky, send me these items and I often use PVC clothing as an umbrella term for
everything PU coated but as I already said this is real PVC and this is a raincoat. I always wanted
to like try on and show a raincoat, I think it's the first time, just going to put it over this catsuit.
And buttoned it up. By the way the buttons are made of rubber as well.
And I do have a belt too so I should put this all around.
I decided on a see-through PVC here and also the matte version because I thought this is going to be a really nice look
with the black contrast stitching
and the black outfit I'm wearing underneath
and I think I was right
The look is really cute kind of girly look with the white trail here
And I can also close this to give it a bit more, I don't know, straight wipe.
Let me check.
Oh yeah, there's another button up here.
Now that is a totally different look.
It's not as playful anymore.
It's more like a trench coat somehow.
But I still like it.
I also love the design element here with the flap from the side.
which is asymmetrical and yeah still happy to have chosen this option with this color because
I think you can also wear like a colorful outfit underneath and you can still see it through
and with the colorless pvc you have like cool second layer I'm going to open it again
because I think I prefer the open look. It's really easy to open the buttons actually
and the color. Yeah I think I prefer this look because it's more I don't know playful and
feminine with the open color and yeah it also looks it feels really high quality. I'm going to
tell you more about the material and but before that I'm going to change into the next outfit.
Now this catsuit, the blue one, I also have a red one, is loose fit. It's really easy to get into of course.
and this is the intended look so it's great for wearing when it rains it basically is rainwear
all of you like that particular kind of outfits with this kind of yeah loose fit and look so this
PVC is really soft like all three of them feel really soft it is not really stretchy so if you're
looking for that in a fabric so compared to latex for example which is really stretchy then
this is a nice firm option so not stretchy at all basically also great if you have a latex
for example because this is not latex but it has a kind of yeah a similar look
or at least a bit. There's also a hood which I can put on. Now I'm like a smurf and the seams
are welded. So with the white coat we had fabric stitching on top of that, so at the headlines
basically. But normally with this one and this one and also the seams here in between they're welded.
It's a bit like like the latex technique. And the specialty here is that the key points where
there's a lot of tension are specifically reinforced. So basically you take a patch
of the material and apply glue and weld it to the garment applying pressure so it sticks together
which yeah makes the material stronger and more durable. Candy Coated US is the sister company to
make it kinky and if you're also interested in this kind of special reinforcement in the areas
where there's a lot of tension. You can write it on email, I am sure you can figure something out.
I think it's a really cool feature to pre-launch into the life cycle of your PVC clothing.
So whereas this was really loose fit, the next one is going to be really tight and I will change.
The red one and I think it contrasts nicely with my hair but also with the PVC underwear I'm
wearing beneath it to show you how cool that looks and this cut is a bit more
complex than with the blue one we have bus seams here and we have the zipper
that runs through the crotch to the backside it's a three-way zipper also
the zipper goes up right up onto the hood here there's another zipper so you
can close it completely but be careful with that anyway I think it's a really
cool look so the material itself is a bit sticky if you like it that way you
can just leave it like that or if you want to have a bit of smoother slippery
feeling just wash it as you do with latex and what I did I put a bit of
of B-Gloss or silicone oil in my washing water and just rinse the garment in that and then
let it dry. You can also spray B-Gloss on a towel and pull it through the arms and legs
so it doesn't stick as much. It depends on the way you prefer it. I think these are cool
options you have here. And I'm kinda badass in this outfit. I think it could also work
as a cosplay outfit for example or if you just want to wear it to the bedroom.
I'm going to close the zipper as far as it's comfortable like with the collar.
Yeah maybe like this. And as for the smell because you may imagine that it
does smell a bit it does and it reminded me a bit of the inflatable beach balls
from my childhood. I hope you can imagine the smell now and I think it's part of
it. Now question goes out to my community does any one of you have experience with PVC fashion?
What do you like about it? What can you recommend? Any tips for handling it? Let me know in the
comments and I have to say that I'm surprised that it is not as noisy as I thought it would be.
So you have some other fabrics where you can really hear it sticking together and being
I don't know thick but this one sounds as smooth as it looks and with that I think I am at the end
here let me know which one was your favorite I really love the look with the raincoat I also
love this look here with the contrast of the undergarments and really bright red with my hair
so I think these two were my favorites. Leave a thumbs up, check out Make It Kinky. I will put
the link in the description text of course. Thank you to Make It Kinky for collaborating me on this
video and I hope you enjoyed it. I will see you in the next video. Have a nice day. Bye.